<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <template id="report_document_contrct_oblig_templ">
        <div class="page">
                    <div class="oe_structure"/>
            <div style="text-align: center">
                <i>This Proposal when signed by the customer and Jan Fence, Inc will constitute a binding contract.</i></div>
                    <br/>
            <div style="text-align: center">
                    <h2>
                        <strong><u>Contractual Obligations</u></strong>
                    </h2>
            </div>
            <div class="ms16 me16">


                    <ol>
                        <p style="font-size:16px">
                        <strong>
                            1. Charges for Late Payment.
                        </strong>
                        If we do not receive full payment within 10 days after it is due,
                            you will be responsible for a late payment charge of 5% of the
                            unpaid amount or $10.00, whichever is greater. You will be responsible
                            for all costs involved should nonpayment require third party intervention.
                            This includes but is not limited to court fees, lawyer fees and any other service
                            needed to finalize the Contracts terms. Nonpayment will also void your warranty
                            status with Jan Fence, Inc.
                    </p>
                    </ol>
                    <ol>
                        <p style="font-size:16px">
                        <strong>
                            2. Change in Address.
                        </strong>
                        You must notify us in writing within 30 days of any change in your address.
                        </p>
                    </ol>
                    <ol>
                        <p style="font-size:16px">
                        <strong>
                            3. Official Fees, Taxes and Fines.
                        </strong>
                        You must promptly pay all official fees and taxes, if applicable, related to this installation,
                            including permit fees, inspection fees and personal property taxes. Some bills for official
                            fees and taxes may be sent to you for payment. Other bills may be paid by us on your behalf,
                            and we will charge you the amount paid. You must pay all fees incurred during the installation,
                            even if they are assessed and billed after the installation has ended. We may charge you an
                            estimated amount for the remaining fees at the end of the installation. You are responsible
                            for any shortage in this estimate, and we will refund you any excess.
                        </p>
                    </ol>
                    <ol>
                        <p style="font-size:16px">
                        <strong>
                            4. Installation.
                        </strong>
                        We shall furnish and install a fence as agreed upon previously and any additional work as
                            described herein at the address listed on the reverse. We agree to complete coverage,
                            except in omitted areas. We shall be permitted to make all necessary alterations in its
                            judgement required to accomplish the work to be performed. We will make every effort to
                            avoid damage to lawn, shrubs, and property, but by reason of the nature of the work are
                            not responsible for any damage caused during installation.
                        </p>
                    </ol>
                    <ol>
                        <p style="font-size:16px">
                        <strong>
                            5. Completion Date.
                        </strong>
                        We shall make a good faith effort to complete the installation on or about the date mentioned
                            herein. If completion date is not met by us, we shall not be held responsible for any delay.
                        </p>
                    </ol>
            <ol>
                        <p style="font-size:16px">
                        <strong>
                            6. Boundaries.
                        </strong>
                        You will provide an accurate survey or diagram of the property boundaries upon which we may rely.
                            You will indemnify any claims arising from the location of the fence.
                        </p>

                    </ol>
            <ol>
                        <p style="font-size:16px">
                        <strong>
                            7. Permits.
                        </strong>
                        You will obtain and be responsible for the cost of the necessary permits and variances.
                        </p>

                    </ol>
            <ol>
                        <p style="font-size:16px">
                        <strong>
                            8. Indemnification.
                        </strong>
                        Unless Jan Fence’s own negligence, you shall defend, hold harmless Jan Fence, its employees,
                            officers, directors, and affiliates from any cost, expense, or damage claimed by third
                            parties for property damage and/or bodily injury, including death, which arises from or is
                            related to the installation, use, maintenance, or operation of the fence system and/or any
                            work performed by Jan Fence to the greatest extent permitted by law.
                        </p>

                    </ol>
            <ol>
                        <p style="font-size:16px">
                        <strong>
                            9. Limited Liability.
                        </strong>
                        You shall in no manner hold Jan Fence, its employees, officers, directors, and affiliates
                            liable for bodily injury or property damages resulting from and/or inflicted to underground
                            pipes, wires, cables, invisible dog fences, pool lines or any other underground structure
                            that is not clearly marked on a surveyor diagram of location to scale, of for the improper
                            placement of the fence. Furthermore, we shall not be responsible for empty ground space due
                            to rocky conditions, property grading or heavily sloped areas. You are responsible for all
                            repairs of any damage outlined within this paragraph and for all property boundaries.
                        </p>

                    </ol>
            <ol>
                        <p style="font-size:16px">
                        <strong>
                            10. Notices.
                        </strong>
                        All correspondence and notices will be sent to the billing address shown on the Contract unless you give us an alternate address in writing.
                        </p>

                    </ol>
            <ol>
                        <p style="font-size:16px">
                        <strong>
                            11. Choice of Law Severability.
                        </strong>
                        You agree that the law of the State of New Jersey applies to this Contract. If certain
                            provisions of this contract violate the law, those provisions will be void, and the
                            rest of the Contract will be enforceable. The venue of any litigation under this agreement
                            shall be in a court of competent jurisdiction in the State of New Jersey.
                        </p>

                    </ol>
            <ol>
                        <p style="font-size:16px">
                        <strong>
                            12. No Waiver by Us.
                        </strong>
                        If we delay or refrain from exercising our rights under this Contract, we do not lose those
                            rights. If we accept late or partial payments from you, we do not waive our rights to
                            receive full and timely payments.
                        </p>

                    </ol>
            <ol>
                        <p style="font-size:16px">
                        <strong>
                            13. Modification or Amendment.
                        </strong>
                        No amendment, change or modification of this Contract shall be valid unless in writing and signed by both parties hereto.
                        </p>

                    </ol>
            <ol>
                        <p style="font-size:16px">
                        <strong>
                            14. Miscellaneous.
                        </strong>
                        All material is guaranteed to be as specified. All work to be completed in a workmanlike manner
                            according to standard practices. Any alteration or deviation from the within specifications
                            involving extra cost will be done only upon a written change order. The costs will become an
                            extra charge over and above the estimate. All elements of this agreement are contingent upon
                            strikes, accidents, or delays beyond our control. The estimate does not include material price
                            increases or additional labor and materials which may be required should unforeseen problems
                            arise after the work has commenced.
                        </p>

                    </ol>
            <ol>
                        <p style="font-size:16px">
                        <strong>
                            15. NJ Department of Consumer Affairs Consumer Service Center Hotline.
                        </strong>
                         (973) 504-6200, Toll Free (NJ Only): 800-242-5846.
                        </p>

                    </ol>
            <ol>
                        <p style="font-size:16px">
                        <strong>
                            16. Insurance.
                        </strong>
                         A copy of the certificate of commercial general liability insurance can be obtained upon request. The telephone of the insurance company issuing the certificate is (973) 256-7703
                        </p>

                    </ol>
            <div style="text-align: center">
                <strong>
                    <u>Two Year Labor Warranty</u>
                        </strong>
                <br/>
            </div>
            <p style="font-size:16px">
                Jan Fence, Inc warrants only the original purchaser that all new fencing is free from defects in
                material and workmanship, under normal and proper usage. This warranty only applies to defects resulting
                from normal use and not from changes by alteration, abuse, fire, flood, unstable soil, underground water
                conditions, checking, warping, and “Acts of God”. Under this warranty, obligation is limited to replacement
                of the defective material this warranty gives you specific legal rights and may also have other rights
                which may vary from state to state.
            </p>
                </div>
                </div>
    </template>

</odoo>
